https://conflictcenter.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY:
Who we are
Our website address is www.conflictcenter.org.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
This site uses contact forms and registration forms to gather personal information. Submissions are kept indefinitely for customer service purposes. Unless consent is expressly given at the bottom of each form, we do not use the information submitted for marketing purposes. This site uses Gravity Forms for contact and registration forms. Their privacy policy can be viewed here: https://www.gravityforms.com/privacy/
Opt-in forms
This site uses opt-in forms to collect your name and email for marketing purposes so we can notify you about related content and special offers. Submissions are kept indefinitely. If you submit an opt-in form on our site you will be opting in for us to save your name, email address and other relevant information. You can opt our or unsubscribe at any time in the future by clicking the unsubscribe link in the bottom of any email. Specifically The Conflict Center uses MailChimp. Their privacy Policy can be viewed here: https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
We use anonymous cookies to prevent users from seeing the same popup repetitively in an attempt to make our users experience more pleasant while still delivering time sensitive messaging.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
This site uses the Google Analytics to see how visitors find and use our website.
Who we share your data with
All personal information collected on contact or opt-in forms is shared with MailChimp and their privacy policy can be viewed here: https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
Subscriber information is retained in the local database indefinitely for analytic tracking purposes and for future export. Data will be exported or removed upon users request. Data is retained in MailChimp until unsubscribed or deleted and will be removed upon users request.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, filled out a contact or opt-in form, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Contact information
The Conflict Center
4140 Tejon Street
Denver, CO 80211
303-433-4983
info@conflictcenter.org
CONTACT PERSON FOR GDPR REQUESTS
Simply put — we teach people to solve problems and build relationships. We want families, schools and communities to put themselves at the center of nonviolence. Our programs equip people with skills to navigate conflict productively.
Adults
Annual Report & Financials
Youth
Register for a class
Contact The Conflict Center
**
CAPTCHACommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
© Copyright 2018 The Conflict Center
| Privacy Policy
